(Places tourists don't go to)
(Places only locals go to)
(The first travel destination, Da Nang, Gyeonggi Province)
(In search of places with no Koreans in Da Nang,)
(a city with lots of Koreans)
(Exploring new travel destinations you've never seen before)
(Out of all these people here, there's not a single Korean person!)
(Travelling in a foreign country where they don't speak the language)
(Body language)
(Mì Quảng.)
(They don't understand us at all.)
(Even with a language barrier, they can still have fun.)
(They don't have a plan, but they have standards.)
(But the trip wasn't all sunshine and rainbows.)
(This was a fail.)
(This can be broadcast, right?)
(I think we came into the wrong place.)
(They must only go to places with no Koreans.)
(Failed to meet their standards?)
(It's only the 2nd episode, and there is an emergency.)
(Resolve the emergency.)
(To a place with only locals)
(Our travel buddies search every corner)
(All of the people from this area are gathered here.)
(Let's find places where locals gather.)
(Eating and eating some more at the place locals picked out)
(Their favourite snack chosen by locals)
(- Do we have this in Korea? - We don't.)
(Let's go even deeper into the local areas.)
(How about we go in even deeper?)
(To truly local places)
(Going even deeper in)
(Filming)
(They took over local social media.)
(Today will be another long day.)
(The meeting of two men)
(The second story of real Vietnam)
(The gentle and peaceful sound of the waves)
(Groaning)
Oh, I think I might die.
(Hyun Moo is at the age where he always wants to lie down.)
(Following Hyun Moo and lying down)
This is a true summer vacation.
Joon, isn't this a true summer vacation?
A nice, gentle breeze.
Listening to the cicadas.
(Underwear)
(Joon is using this spare time to practice SAN's "Bad" challenge.)
I'm feeling great right now.
The best ever.
(Hyun Moo can't believe how energetic Joon is.)
I want to play more.
(Laughing)
You're young.
What's up with me?
- Is it because I exercised?
- It's because you exercised.
I really think so.
(He takes a relaxing nap.)
What should we do now?
What?
We should sleep for four more hours.
- For four more hours?
- Yes.
(Bursting with energy, Joon has no desire to sleep.)
I told you I liked shopping, right?
Should we go shopping?
Your clothes...
Yes?
It's too much.
(Pyjamas)
Your black-and-white look.
(Day 1, Day 2)
You are so odd.
It's embarrassing. You're always wearing that.
- Let's go buy some clothes.
- Okay.
And get some food.
Where should we go?
Have you seen any Koreans here? No, right?
No.
The market I'm planning to go to...
- also has no Koreans.
- Okay.
- It's called Bac My An Market.
It's, of course, a market locals go to.
(Bac My An Market for locals, Han Market full of Korean tourists)
(Han Market is a must-visit spot for tourists in Da Nang.)
(You can hear familiar sounds of Korea in a foreign country.)
(Even if you ask in Korean,)
(the citizens of Da Nang, Gyeonggi Province understand.)
(We don't go to mainstream spots. This is Hyunmoo Road.)
(A place where tourists don't really go, only locals.)
(Bac My An Market is a 10-minute drive from Han Market.)
(Bac My An Market)
(Market vendor: Bac My An Market is a traditional market in Da Nang.)
(Compared to Han Market, many locals come here.)
(It's a traditional market that's been here for 22 years.)
(Fresh ingredients locals enjoy)
(And friendly eateries full of local foods)
(From food to daily goods, it's Da Nang's one-stop shop.)
(Our road leads to Bac My An Market.)
Oh, got it. I like shopping.
Let's go.
That was a nice break. It really was.
(Bai Da Beach, Bac My An Market)
Joon.
- This is that market, I see.
- You need to buy some clothes.
- What should I buy?
- You need to be taught a lesson.
(Hyun Moo will teach Joon a lesson on shopping for clothes.)
You wear the same outfit too many times.
I want to wear traditional clothes.
- Traditional clothes?
- Yes.
Something I can only wear here.
That's nice. Yes.
I think I need to buy a sleeveless shirt like yours.
There's a flower market too.
You really love flowers.
I do.
Do you too?
Now that I'm older, I do.
(Now that he's older, he gets the love for flowers.)
- I think we can go in through here.
- That's right.
- I see lots of clothes.
- We need to buy clothes.
Bac My An Market.
Almost no Koreans.
Going inside when the sun is out.
- How nice is that?
- It is nice.
There aren't so many people.
Right. There aren't so many people.
Not many people.
(You can really feel the local atmosphere here.)
It really feels like Korean markets from back in the day.
You're right. It reminds me of when I was young.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my.
It feels like Korea in the early 1990s.
You always have to get kimchi jjigae at a place like this.
The smell gets on your clothes.
It really does feel like Korea back in the day.
(This traditional Vietnamese market oddly reminds you of Korea.)
Should we try going this way?
I'll have to go refrigerator-style.
I think over refrigerator-style, I prefer short shorts.
Can you wear that around?
Yes, I can.
Why are you punishing yourself...
Oh, yes. This is it.
- There's a lot here.
- This is what I'm talking about.
- That's intense.
- It's super thin.
These kinds of clothes are nice.
It must be a lot nicer if there were just one pattern.
I need to wear shorts.
This place is nice. Oh, yes.
(How about this one?)
Hyun Moo. They have sets here.
- Is this a set?
- Here.
(They spot a colourful resort-style set.)
- It's nice and neat.
- This one is cool.
Wait. This is cool.
What? What a cool vibe.
- This is cool.
- Get whatever you want.
This is cool.
This is a true vacation look.
This just says, "Vacation."
This is it for me.
This is it.
Bao nhiêu... What was it?
Bao nhiêu tiền?
(How much is this? They're getting used to Vietnamese.)
What?
- Một trăm hai mươi nghìn.
- That's...
- It's 10,000.
- Two?
(Một, 1)
- Một.
- Oh, for one.
- So, for two...
- What is this?
- Take off a zero...
- One, ten, hundred, thousand,
ten thousand.
- Zero...
- It's 220,000. So take off a zero.
Then it's 5.50 dollars.
(Oh, my.)
Don't say that.
Look disappointed.
(We have to haggle.)
(Joon is an actor, after all.)
No money.
- Be a bit more disappointed.
- Let's try...
(Joon is wasting his talent on an outfit.)
(The owner is still not interested.)
Can you make it a bit cheaper...
Discount?
- Discount.
Okay?
Two?
(It'll be 100,000 dong per set. Joon's great acting worked.)
This.
- So it's 5 dollars.
- It's 5 dollars?
It's 5 dollars. So 10 dollars for us both.
Ten dollars for us both?
(With his 19 years of acting experience,)
(he got a one-dollar discount.)
(Two-piece resort set 100,000 dong, Total for two sets 200,000 dong)
(Around 10 dollars)
Changing room?
Of course!
(Of course!)
This is the changing room?
(It wasn't there, and now it is?)
(A makeshift changing room)
What is this?
Oh, we change here?
It's a changing room you can see inside.
(These two...)
(are not familiar with this environment...)
- You go ahead.
- Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
It's all see-through.
(Turning down the lights to make it less see-through)
Oh, how chaotic.
What? How unsightly?
You can't see me now, right?
Hyun Moo. It is a bit see-through.
- I'm not wearing underwear.
- I can see you very well.
- Really?
- I'll stand in front.
(He took off his underwear that was wet from playing in the water.)
(His travel buddy Joon will block the view.)
(I'll protect Hyun Moo.)
Oh, this is so nice.
I'm done.
- Are you not wearing any?
- I'm not.
I think it'll be okay. I can't see.
It's so nice. I was almost dying.
It's not see-through. I won't wear any either, then.
Oh, I feel so much better now.
That feels amazing.
Oh, this is nice.
- Isn't it great?
- Oh, my.
(Joon feels liberated too.)
I feel so much better now.
I'm so satisfied.
The happiness of ten dollars.
- Here we go.
- I love it!
- Yes!
- It feels like I'm wearing nothing.
I'm so happy.
(Hyunmoo Road Fashion Week, featuring No Underwear)
It feels like I'm wearing nothing.
(The colourful designs draw attention.)
(You're so handsome, honey.)
Honey.
(He became everyone's honey just with his resort look.)
Yes, I'm your honey.
(This honey is passing by too.)
Honey.
I'm so satisfied.
- Oh, my.
- Super satisfied. I feel amazing.
I think I could wear this for the rest of the trip.
Let's buy several of these sets.
It's so comfortable.
(Day 3 of the trip)
(This is a different day.)
(Day 4 of the trip)
(The same outfit in the next travel destination)
(This is a different day.)
(We're looking forward to Joon's love for resort outfits.)
This place is also a food paradise.
(They're getting a bit hungry after shopping.)
Oh, winkles.
That looks tasty.
(The biggest reason locals love Bac My An Market)
(Bac My An Market is full of food.)
(Sweet desserts)
(Mì Quảng trộn, Vietnamese mixed noodles)
(Cơm cháy, Vietnamese fried burnt rice)
(Bánh căn, Vietnamese mini pancakes)
(Cơm gà, Vietnamese chicken rice)
(Miến trộn, Vietnamese glass noodle salad)
(You can enjoy local food culture here.)
There's a nice restaurant right here.
Oh, my.
That looks good.
Bánh mì.
Bánh mì. Oh, that's famous.
- Bánh mì is famous.
- Yes, bánh mì.
One of my favourite Vietnamese foods...
- is bánh xèo.
- Bánh xèo?
- This looks good.
- This is really good.
- Do you want to try this?
- Should we?
You have to eat bánh xèo.
Hey, they even have suyuk.
(Bánh Tráng Cuốn Thịt Heo, Da Nang-style pork wraps)
- Bánh căn.
- One bánh căn?
- Bánh xèo.
- Okay.
We need to eat a bowl of rice noodles.
- Mì Quảng?
- One Mì Quảng.
- Okay.
(They ordered Mì Quảng too.)
- Bánh căn.
- Oh, it's already here.
(Oh, it's already here.)
Apparently, this is a Nha Trang dish.
This looks good.
(A popular market food in Vietnam's south-central region)
(Bánh căn, Vietnamese mini pancakes)
Oh, that looks delicious.
Like this.
Look at this.
(Moo Friends, take a look at this delicious-looking bánh căn.)
Oh, it's so juicy.
- Is it good?
- Yes!
What is this?
It's a shrimp and what pancake?
It's good.
- Isn't it good?
- It is.
Oh, my. This place is good too.
(This really hits the spot.)
It's good.
(He's really liking it.)
The batter and the starch are savoury.
It's like the Vietnamese version of egg bread.
(The savoury fried starch makes the pancake...)
(perfectly crunchy on the outside and moist on the inside.)
I love this spicy part. This.
I like the chilli.
(Meanwhile, the owner is preparing the next dish.)
(Thick noodles, nutty peanuts, vegetables, meat, and seafood)
(A popular noodle dish of Central Vietnam with a mix of flavours)
(Mì Quảng, Vietnamese mixed rice noodles)
- Mì Quảng.
Mì Quảng.
It's different from the Mì Quảng at the other place.
(Local market Mì Quảng, Locally recommended Mì Quảng)
(You can enjoy Mì Quảng in many ways with different ingredients.)
Look at this. There's broth in here.
- You're right.
- There is.
We have to mix it.
(Mì Quảng: A rice noodle dish with a saucy soup...)
(from the central region of Vietnam)
We have to eat this until we get sick of it.
Is this place good too?
It's good.
Mì Quảng tastes different in each place.
- Bánh xèo.
It comes with a lot of things.
This is bánh xèo.
I've never had this before.
It's tasty.
I even go to specific restaurants with good bánh xèo.
They have this a lot in Korea too, right?
It doesn't taste like it does here.
(A famous Vietnamese dish, bánh xèo)
(Bánh xèo, Vietnamese pancakes)
- What is that?
- I see.
- It's rice paper.
- Oh, rice paper.
Bánh xèo.
(Rice paper)
Oh, yes.
(Joon puts it in his mouth right away.)
Not like that.
Oh, we need to wrap it.
- Oh, in here?
- Oh, rice paper.
- Oh, like that?
- I see.
Okay.
Oh, my. That looks delicious.
- I see. Okay.
- Go ahead.
- Yes, dip it in there.
- Go ahead, Hyun Moo.
- No, you go. Okay.
- No, go.
You should try it too... Oh, that's hot!
Oh, that's hot.
(The heat from the freshly cooked bánh xèo makes him scream.)
Oh, open it like that.
(Meanwhile, Joon is reviewing how to eat bánh xèo.)
Okay.
(Preparing his chopsticks)
In here.
This looks delicious.
Oh, my!
(Pupils dilating)
Oh, my.
- When I went to Hanoi, - Yes.
I went to a bánh xèo restaurant with one Michelin star.
It's better than that place.
- This is so good.
- Seriously.
This place has great bánh xèo.
This is so good!
It's better than the place with one Michelin star.
(The savoury flavour spreads through their mouths.)
Their bánh xèo is amazing.
This is so good.
(What do you think of my cooking?)
It's so fun to eat the rice paper without wetting it with water.
It feels like eating it with wallpaper for your house.
It's similar to Korean ssam culture.
Totally.
(Even Vietnam's food culture is similar to Korea's.)
- I wasn't even that hungry.
- Same.
But I can't stop eating.
(Joon is in love with his first-ever bánh xèo.)
(Moved)
This is the tastiest thing I've eaten in Vietnam so far.
- Right? Isn't bánh xèo good?
- This is the best.
(I'm glad they like it.)
What if we had missed this place?
Seriously.
We've had breakfast and lunch so far.
Yes.
Both were a success.
You don't miss Korean food, right?
Not at all.
It's so good.
(Even the way they eat is so similar.)
(For a moment, they forgot about Korean food.)
It feels like I'm eating Vietnamese food for the first time.
This is so good.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Delicious.
- Delicious.
- Yummy.
Thank you.
We could eat so many meals in this market.
- Vietnamese Gen Zers...
- Yes.
post short-form content...
with avocado ice cream you can get here.
What?
- Avocado ice cream?
- We need to try some.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
- We need to eat this.
- It looks good.
We need to eat this.
Avocado ice cream.
(Over many other ice creams,)
(this one took over the algorithms of Vietnamese Gen Zers.)
(From Gen Z to the elderly, everyone loves this trendy snack.)
(We'll go and try it now.)
- Let's pay.
How much?
(How much is a meal at a local market?)
Ninety.
- Okay.
- Ninety.
(90,000 dong)
So that's 90,000 dong. Take off a zero...
It's 4.50 dollars.
- It's 4.50 dollars for all of this?
- Yes.
Goodness.
- Bye.
Bye.
- Is this the place?
- I think it is.
(A 1-second walk from the bánh xèo store)
- Yes. Sit down.
- They're right next to each other.
- Oh, here it is.
- This is that trendy...
avocado ice cream.
(Avocado ice cream, Kem bơ)
- Kem bơ.
- Should we eat a small?
- We'd like kem bơ...
- Do you want a small?
- A small.
- I want a medium.
- Medium?
- Small, medium. One, one.
- One, one.
(A small for Joon, a medium for Hyun Moo)
Sit down.
- Where...
- Oh, my.
I think we walked 1m.
Everyone is eating that.
(Some enjoy eating it at the store.)
(Kem bơ, Kem bơ)
(Some enjoy getting take-out.)
(Some enjoy getting this national snack delivered.)
Can you only find this here? In Vietnam?
It's popular in Vietnam.
Like how matcha was popular in Korea.
- Small?
- Medium.
- Medium. Small.
- Small.
(Again, their order comes out right away.)
I don't think you can find this in Korea.
- You can't.
- This look.
(Avocado,)
(sweet ice cream,)
(and crunchy coconut chips make a beautiful combination.)
(Kem bơ: Avocado ice cream)
(We have to get a picture of this.)
Vietnamese Gen Z.
(Trying out Vietnamese Gen Z trends)
(It's cold.)
- The coconut chips.
- Oh, my!
Coconut chips and vanilla ice cream.
Hyun Moo, this is totally my style.
This is so delicious!
Why do you think so? It's the coconut.
This combination is insane. This right here.
- Coconut chips.
- Yes.
- You like coconut.
- It's so good.
These three things. The avocado,
the vanilla,
- Coconut chips.
- the coconut chips.
- They go insanely well together.
- Yes, the combination.
It's a good idea.
(Joon can't put his spoon down.)
- This is kind of...
- Yes?
something they'd serve as dessert at restaurants...
with lots of Michelin stars.
- Like at a hotel?
- Yes, don't you think so?
- It's such a sophisticated flavour.
- You're right.
This is so well made.
(It gets three Joonchelin stars.)
This is truly Michelin level. This is insane.
(Michelin?)
(Tapping his shoulder)
Is it good?
Good.
(The owner is proud.)
(Staring)
- Gosh, this is insane.
- Coconut?
(If you eat well, you can get free coconut chip refills.)
Coconut?
(Thank you.)
Oh, gosh. She's really generous with you.
Without the coconut chips, it could've been a bit boring.
- Right. This makes it good.
- Yes.
Oh, this is so good.
The coconut chips really make it good. It's so good.
(The compliments and generosity make the dessert even sweeter.)
Every time I eat something, I think it's my favourite.
This is number one for me.
You say that every time you eat something.
It keeps getting better.
- What a brilliant idea.
- That was so good.
(This visit to the local market was full of flavour and kindness.)
Is there anything else you want to do?
What do you want to do?
- Massage?
- Let's go.
- Massage. Let's go.
Okay.
(Total: approximately 17 dollars)
- Bye.
(This is Hyunmoo Road)
Let's try going this way.
(They freely roam the peaceful city.)
(While roaming around, they naturally find these places.)
This is a massage paradise.
(A must-do activity in Vietnam is to go to a massage studio.)
(Where have these two arrived in massage paradise?)
I see lots of Koreans.
They're so Korean.
They're Korean, right?
- They're all Korean.
- You're right.
A place only locals go, not tourists.
It's definitely in there somewhere.
- Hello.
- Have a fun trip. Thank you.
- Nice to see you.
(Koreans everywhere)
- Hello.
- Nice to see you.
There are lots of Korean people. This trip is a fail.
Sorry. Let me get a picture with you!
(It's like a fan meet-and-greet.)
- Cheese.
- Thank you.
Thank you!
(Will this trip be okay like this?)
We need to be careful here. This is...
- the Han River.
- Okay.
- The Han Market.
- Yes.
Koreans all come here.
(The Han River, a main tourist spot in Da Nang.)
(And right in front of the Han River is...)
(Han Market)
(It's always bursting with people,)
(especially many Korean tourists.)
(Korean Family Karaoke, There's Korean written everywhere.)
Basically everyone on that side of the street is Korean.
You're right.
(They must be shooting something!)
- So my plan...
- Yes.
is not to go to places that say "massage" in Korean.
(Must avoid signs that say "massage" in Korean.)
- That's your plan?
- Yes.
A lot of Koreans will definitely be there.
I think it'll be harder to find places without Korean signs.
Let's try to look.
(A mission to uphold our standards, Find a shop without a Korean sign.)
Are there no places without Korean signs?
Let's go this way.
(They embark on an unexpected adventure.)
Oh, gosh. This is basically Korea.
- It's Myeongdong.
- Dead skin removal.
Eyelash extensions. Yes.
This is basically Myeongdong.
There's more Korean than Myeongdong.
- Oh, it says, "Hello..." - "Hello." "Pharmacy."
- No, we can't go there.
- "Massage."
- It's all in Korean.
- No, we can't go there.
(Are there any massage studios without Korean people?)
From here on, everyone in front of us are all Koreans.
- I can tell at a glance.
- Yes.
- At a glance.
- Just at a glance, right?
Nothing here.
Okay.
(They walk and walk some more.)
I'm sure there's a place without Koreans.
Hey, this place has no Korean.
"Onda."
(This place has no Korean! "Onda")
- They're not Korean.
- Are they...
- They're not.
- Nice.
- Hello.
- She's Korean...
- Oh, my!
Are you Korean?
- Yes.
- Oh, my!
- They're all Korean.
- All of them are Korean.
Oh, my gosh!
We're looking for nice Vietnamese places...
without any Koreans.
As soon as we entered, everyone was Korean.
Are you also Korean? Oh, gosh.
- I think we're at the wrong place.
- This place is famous.
No.
- Is this a famous place?
- Yes.
(Many Koreans come here.)
Someone was here.
- Moon So Ri was here.
- Actress Moon So Ri was here.
(It's me, Moon So Ri.)
Wait, I think we need to accept these.
- They brought us tea.
- I think we need to drink it.
So, we won't film here.
Yes. Because we need to go to places without Koreans.
This doesn't fit our standards.
The end.
(The end.)
(We didn't shoot at this location...)
(because it didn't fit Hyunmoo Road standards.)
(We ask for your kind understanding.)
(From now on, we'll listen to the audio.)
(Oh, my... This is amazing.)
This is amazing.
(We couldn't show these places because there were many Koreans.)
Feels so good.
(Here are lots of inserts from those tourist spots.)
(Uncles, please come back soon.)
(Man, they're loud.)
(Time to wake up!)
(After the massage,)
(Hyun Moo gets a recommendation for a restaurant with no Koreans.)
Can you tell me where the best restaurant is?
I recommend this place.
- Vietnamese?
- Yes, Vietnamese.
- Seafood.
- Sea what?
- "Haesanmul." - Oh, seafood.
(Laughing)
Thank you!
That's hilarious.
They must be getting off work.
(Let's go home and eat.)
(Away from the bright and noisy city,)
(they head to a quiet neighbourhood with dim street lights.)
(It's quiet near the entrance.)
There's no one here.
What is this place?
(People's voices break the silence.)
(The kids were playing in the alley.)
It's just like how we used to play when we were kids.
Just like the old days.
(They find a scene similar to Korea in a small alley.)
- Yes.
- They're adorable.
Hide-and-seek...
I wish I could join them.
Are they playing freeze tag?
- What is it?
- Is it soccer?
- Soccer? It's soccer.
- Oh, they're playing soccer.
- Hello.
Hello.
Together?
(Sure.)
- Rock, paper, scissors.
Yes, I won! I'm going to kick it.
Rock, paper, scissors! Okay!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors! Why are we doing this, though?
Rock, paper, scissors.
- Great.
- Rock, paper, scissors.
- All right.
Rock, paper, scissors.
All right.
Rock, paper, scissors. Yes!
- Rock, paper, scissors.
- You beat all of them?
Every single one.
- I won. Rock, paper, scissors.
- They're terrible at this.
How did they all lose?
- Yes!
- What is going on?
Yes! I beat all of them.
Rock, paper, scissors. Yes!
- Rock, paper, scissors.
- How is this possible?
(He finally lost after 13 wins.)
Still, you're like...
Messi in the world of rock-paper-scissors.
(Here's how Messi plays.)
Pass!
(Running desperately)
(At this moment, he feels like Messi.)
Higher!
(Is it us, or do they look like they're having the most fun?)
(Grabbing)
Go long.
(Pass it to me!)
You're so bad.
(Joon is embarrassed and laughs it off.)
(Hyun Moo is exhausted after running for a few minutes.)
- Just one more time.
- How are they still going?
(The kids don't care and start the second half.)
He's good. He's like Lee Kang In.
You must be the future of Vietnamese soccer.
(The future national athlete's fancy turn)
(Incredible speed)
- He's so fast.
- How is he so fast?
Get back!
(Hyun Moo and Joon get a proper workout in...)
- Pass.
- Go away.
Go away.
(in the middle of the night.)
- I'm so out of shape.
- I'm tired.
I'm exhausted.
Hey, Kang In.
Calm down.
(Screaming)
Stop! Please stop!
Hey.
(Staggering)
- I'm so tired.
- We can't keep up.
(Shaking)
This is so tough.
And they were in slippers.
Gosh. That's insane.
(They're all wearing slippers.)
I didn't know that was possible.
Let's go. That's enough.
- Bye-bye.
Bye.
- Good night.
- See you.
(Still out of breath after playing soccer under the moonlight)
I ran for a few seconds, and I'm sweating buckets.
He was so fast.
He was. And that was in slippers.
You know,
- the masseuse...
- Yes.
recommended it.
(They were looking for the restaurant.)
Where are we? It's a common neighbourhood.
Are we at the right place?
There's a diner here?
I can't imagine anyone walking by this place.
They're all private houses.
This looks like a housing area.
Isn't that it? The bright one.
- Where?
- Up ahead.
(They keep looking around to find it.)
There are so many people.
It's so crowded.
Everyone in the neighbourhood is here.
It's crowded all of a sudden.
- That's amazing.
- Look at that place.
(It looks like everyone in the neighbourhood is here.)
This place...
is huge.
(Not many Koreans know about this large diner.)
(It feels like they're in the right place.)
(From Bac My An Market to this diner)
These two are the same place.
These two?
What an extreme neighbourhood.
(Two large buildings are filled with locals.)
Are there any seats?
What is this place?
(Joon is intimidated by the overwhelming size.)
Okay.
They show us to a table after we order our food.
Crayfish.
One or two?
That's crayfish.
This is their best one.
One or two?
Two? Yes, two.
- It's barbecue.
- Barbecue?
- Steam and barbecue.
- Yes, steam and barbecue.
It's better to steam and barbecue it, right?
You're right.
Prawns? Okay.
Half a kilogram.
Half a kilo? Good.
(Adding tiger prawns)
Okay.
In Vietnam, seafood is called "hải sản."
(Various types of fresh seafood are everywhere in the restaurant.)
Da Nang is in central Vietnam, and thanks to its long coastline,
you can enjoy fresh and diverse seafood on a budget.
(There are tons of colourful dishes crafted from fresh seafood.)
At first, we became popular for selling food at low prices.
More tourists visit in this season than in the winter.
More customers from Hanoi visit us...
in the summer.
There are all these people,
and I don't see any Koreans.
I ordered one that looked like a lobster.
Okay.
- That and 500g of prawns.
- Yes.
And I heard their clams were good.
Clams? Should we order those too?
We should.
Is this...
like Garak Market in Korea?
The night market in Jongro.
You know Jongro is popular these days, right?
Oh, that's what it's like.
Okay.
There's no English.
(It's only in Vietnamese.)
Seashell?
(He describes it with his body.)
(Looking for a translator app)
(Hyun Moo desperately wants clams.)
(Are you talking about this?)
What is it? This is also in Vietnamese.
(He showed Hyun Moo the Vietnamese word.)
Scallop?
- Scallop!
- Scallop?
- Yes, scallop!
- Scallop!
- How did he know that word?
- Right?
How did he know?
Oh, man.
(Tôm sú nuog mọi, Salt-grilled tiger prawn)
Should we eat?
I lost my appetite.
(He worked out and lost his appetite.)
Do we eat the whole thing?
Hold on. I'll take this off.
- There you go.
- Just the head.
And...
dip it here.
(Will it be good enough to bring back Hyun Moo's appetite?)
It's good.
(He has no appetite, but he gives it a try.)
(Carefully taking a bite)
- It's good.
- It's so good.
It's good.
The prawns were grilled over charcoal,
so they have a smoky flavour.
(Tiger prawn bursting with smoky flavour)
The charcoal you're talking about is right there.
Right. No wonder it tastes good.
It has that flavour.
(Grilling over an open flame for a smoky flavour)
This is totally my style.
It's not even expensive.
Look at the flesh.
I'm sweating so much because of that Vietnamese Lee Kang In.
I'm still sweating.
It's so hot.
I can't stop sweating.
(Rau muống xào, Stir-fried water spinach)
Scallop.
(Sò điệp nướng, Grilled scallops)
The scallop was cooked so well. What is this?
It's really good.
(A flavour that wakes you up)
It's amazing, isn't it?
This is really good.
This...
You have to put the whole thing in your mouth at once.
Peanuts.
I think it has peanuts, a spicy sauce,
cheongyang pepper,
and garlic flakes.
Who wouldn't like this?
They're really good with combinations.
It tastes really good.
The scallops are amazing.
This one.
Vietnamese food really suits Korean tastes.
Isn't that right?
(We have some broth!)
(Nghêu hấp, Steamed clams)
This is amazing.
Is this like...
mussel soup?
No. It's like clam soup.
Clear clam soup.
This is a familiar taste.
- One you have with alcohol.
- It's a familiar taste.
(Steamed clams with a flavour similar to clam soup)
It's a taste we know.
Right? It's a familiar taste.
It would be perfect with soju.
It's similar to the Korean dish.
The difference...
is that the broth has a cilantro flavour.
- Just a bit.
- Yes.
But it doesn't taste strange.
It's still nice, isn't it?
It's tasty.
The main dish isn't here yet.
You're right.
I'm almost mad that I'm getting full.
Do you eat a lot of food when you drink?
It depends.
I usually eat more.
It's Friday night, but not many people...
are drinking beer.
I just looked around to see what they're eating.
They drink Coke more.
It feels like Vietnamese people don't drink so much.
- That's right.
- It's an atmosphere...
that definitely calls for alcohol, but...
(A restaurant the locals come to have a late dinner)
The Gen Z people in Korea also don't drink so much.
I heard the younger generation don't like being tipsy.
Really? I envy them so much.
I get like this after two glasses.
- That's good.
- I doze off.
You won the Grand Award at the Entertainment Awards.
It's such a happy day.
You still wouldn't drink?
On days like that, people make you drink.
I drink once or twice...
and throw away the third.
Then I act like I'm drunk.
Really?
Then you go home, right?
(Acting like he's drunk)
Manager, please take Hyun Moo home.
I can stay.
Give me a glass.
I do that as well.
I do the same thing.
I do that at gatherings.
And when the door shuts...
(When the door shuts)
- That's right.
- Let's go, Manager.
That's right.
I act so well.
I'm good at doing this.
(Hyun Moo is an expert at acting drunk.)
- Okay!
- No way!
Okay.
Crayfish! Lobster.
This is really...
(Tôm hùm đất nướng bơ, Butter-grilled crayfish)
This is their signature dish.
This is crazy.
Goodness. Look at how plump it is.
See if you can taste a difference from regular lobster.
Okay.
It's chewy.
(It has a chewy texture.)
It's really good.
The way I see it,
it would have been...
really vicious when it was in the sea.
Crayfish is also considered a luxury ingredient in Vietnam.
This seafood is very popular in Vietnam...
because you can really taste its freshness and quality.
It can be enjoyed in many different ways,
including grilled, steamed, fried, and stir-fried.
What's that?
- What's going on?
- What kind of show is this?
Who is she?
(Presenter and local coordinator...)
(responsible for sharing local culture and information)
I thought this was a different show.
We're only supporting actors.
We're just reenactment actors.
In the background.
Hello.
While filming this,
there's something I'm worried about.
I only had fun without thinking about the show.
That would make this show a big hit.
Really?
If the viewers know what we do for the show,
they won't watch it then.
I feel like I'm just having fun, forgetting the camera is there.
I'm not even wearing underwear.
- So...
- I'm not wearing my underwear.
We're both over 40...
I'm soon turning 50.
And this place itself is amazing.
I've been abroad for many shows,
but every famous place was filled with Korean people.
It felt like we were always behind.
(The kind of trip where he always felt like he was a step behind)
It's not because we're celebrities.
- You don't have to be a celebrity.
- You don't have to be one.
When Korean people go abroad,
they don't like places with many Koreans.
We're not trying to see or experience amazing things.
We're just putting ourselves in an environment...
that's completely different from Korea.
That heals you.
(That's when the real healing begins.)
I also like this because it's simple.
We didn't do anything big.
- So, when I was at the airport, - Yes.
- I booked a train ticket.
- What?
- A train?
- We have to do this as we planned.
- Okay.
Because...
it was the only thing I had in mind in Korea.
Vietnam's Gyeongju.
That's nice. Gyeongju is nice.
It's nice.
But it takes four hours to get there.
So we need to set our minds to it.
It's a long trip.
That's why I booked the train tickets...
when I arrived at the airport.
- It's for tomorrow morning.
- Really?
- Tomorrow morning's train?
- Yes.
Travelling by train abroad is really romantic.
It is romantic.
I like that.
Then today's the last night at our accommodation.
That's right.
- I want to go swimming then.
- You can go swimming.
I'll swim then.
You can enjoy your time.
Okay.
Nice. Let's go.
(Total: approximately 121 dollars)
- Today was so amazing.
- Let's go.
- Thank you for the food.
- I'm so full.
It's so nice.
(It's their last night in Da Nang. It's too good to waste on sleep.)
(Screaming)
(Joon enjoys a swim in the pool at their accommodation.)
This is nice.
- Is it warm?
- It's nice. It's cool.
(He dips himself in cool water...)
Nice.
(and washes away the fatigue from the day.)
- The water is refreshing.
- You have amazing shoulders.
Really?
(Should I show off my shoulders a bit?)
I want to take all my clothes off and have fun.
Take it off.
("This is Hyunmoo Road" is just as good as "Solo's Inferno.")
Look at those shoulders and back muscles.
But it's so...
It's such a waste.
(Should I, then?)
(Do you want to join?)
But two men in a pool...
(Hyun Moo wants to refuse.)
That just gives me goosebumps.
(It gives him goosebumps just imagining that.)
But it's really nice.
It's much better than you think.
What is that?
What is that? Wait a minute.
(He stepped on something inside the swimming pool.)
What is that?
What is that? Wait a minute.
- What is that?
- What is it? Is there a bug?
I stepped on something. What was that?
I stepped on something. Hold on.
(He's worried, but he doesn't move.)
I'm scared. What is it?
What is it?
It's an insect! Hold on.
(He's terrified.)
What is this?
What is it?
- A dead insect?
- It's not an insect.
(Shaking)
It was weird.
I need to check. Otherwise, I won't be able to have fun.
(Unlike what he said, he's holding tight.)
What was it?
(What's the mysterious creature that caused the stir?)
Seriously. What is this?
(Even Hyun Moo is at a loss for words.)
This feels terrifying in the water.
I couldn't see it.
Who left this here?
Earlier, this...
I looked pathetic, didn't I?
An insect!
Wait a minute!
(Joon has good self-awareness.)
It didn't suit those shoulders.
Two men are having so much fun.
- Let's go to sleep.
- Good night.
- Aren't you going to sleep?
- I'll stay for a bit.
- All right.
- I'll enjoy this place.
Have fun.
(Hyun Moo leaves first.)
(He tries to ease the sadness of the passing of another day alone.)
(Day 3 of the Vietnam Trip)
(Da Nang Station)
This is Da Nang Station.
- There aren't any Koreans here.
- Not even one.
- Not a single Korean.
- I feel free.
(The train station is filled with local travellers.)
(We're going on a trip.)
This is where we're going.
- Vietnam's Gyeongju.
Huế.
(Huế, Vietnam's Gyeongju)
It's where the last dynasty of Vietnam was.
(A city where the legacy of Vietnam's last dynasty lives on)
It's also a culinary destination.
(A culinary destination with a wide variety of flavours)
It is known for its imperial cuisine.
- Fancy food.
- Really?
(An ancient Vietnamese city with its traditional flavours and charm)
It takes four hours from Da Nang.
People never go there when they come on a package tour.
We're not late for the train, right?
We're not late. We booked the tickets, so it's fine.
Look at all the people. My gosh.
There's a lot...
(The station is crowded with people.)
It's 6:30am,
- but there are so many people.
- It's crowded.
(Passengers fill the platform.)
(From locals to international tourists)
There are so many people.
(Let's go on a train trip!)
I can see a train from here. It looks really pretty.
- That's a train, right?
- What?
- Over there.
- It's pretty.
It looks so pretty.
It looks like a toy.
(A magical purple train straight out of a fairy tale)
We have VIP seats.
(VIP seats?)
There's something about the VIP seats that would shock you.
- What is it?
- I'll show you when we get there.
- Really?
- You'll be shocked.
"There's something like this on a train?"
Really? I love such unique things.
We take the KTX a lot in Korea.
Right.
(He's already excited about getting on the train.)
(They head to discover the secret of the train.)
HD2.
Car Three.
So this is how...
(So this is how you get there.)
Which way is the front?
Three.
It's right here. Car Three.
(Amazing!)
Goodness. What is this?
What is this?
No way.
You can enjoy the view.
Nice. Isn't it nice and refreshing?
(A vintage atmosphere)
This is so amazing.
It's like the old European trains.
(The VIP cabin, the only place on the train...)
(where you can enjoy the view outside)
(An interior that preserves Vietnam's past)
(They even have welcome food for VIP guests.)
The heritage train passes through the Hải Vân Pass,
where the beautiful sea and mountains meet.
It's one of the most scenic routes in Vietnam.
(Da Nang Station, Lang Co Station)
(A scenic route where you can enjoy nature instead of the dull highway)
(Huế Station)
(He's amazed.)
We're only taking the popular routes for couples.
Isn't this a trip for couples?
We went swimming together yesterday.
(Memories of a thrilling water adventure)
And at the pool villa...
(They had a heated workout at the pool villa.)
We interviewed while lying down together.
(Even an interview while lying under the same blanket)
This is the worst.
(They're finally leaving.)
We're leaving.
The view would be amazing, right?
It would be amazing.
This is nice.
This train trip is amazing.
It's...
running right next to the village.
- Right.
- Right?
It's really amazing since we can see all the houses.
We can see everything.
(Getting a glimpse of the everyday life in Vietnam)
(A slow train passing through the city)
(The city looks completely different from the train.)
People here are really productive even on the weekend.
It's 7am right now.
- They're all out on motorcycles.
- At 7am.
(They start their day early in the morning.)
(When the train passes by,)
(they each go their own way to their own lives.)
(People making the most of another ordinary day)
Look at that.
It's amazing that they're not sleeping in on a weekend.
Right.
(Maybe that's why he's starting to feel sleepy.)
They're really productive.
(People suddenly head somewhere.)
(Hyun Moo is wondering where everyone is going.)
What is it?
They got something like bánh mì.
It smells nice.
(The passengers brought back some snacks.)
Aren't you hungry?
I'm getting hungry.
- You're getting hungry?
- Yes.
- Shall we go and check?
- Shall we?
This is amazing.
What is all this?
It's like a theme park.
(The snack bar is the highlight of the train trip.)
It's wild.
We moved one car, and it's a whole new world.
In the old days, they used to sell hard-boiled eggs on the train.
Right. They have that too.
(Hard-boiled eggs bring back memories.)
- Steamed buns too.
- Steamed buns!
She's steaming buns.
(There is a whole array of other traditional...)
It's not just milk tea.
(Vietnamese snacks too.)
One, one, one.
Number one?
Bánh lọc, bánh nậm, nem lụi.
He's singing in the morning!
It's 7am in the morning.
(It's a morning performance for the passengers.)
They are so diligent.
They're singing like that 7am in the morning.
Even professional singers avoid singing this early.
One.
- Should we check out the stage?
- Okay.
(Drawn to the music, the travel buddies move towards the stage.)
(Shall we dance?)
(This turning dance works anywhere in the world.)
Yes!
(They have a dance party at 7am.)
(I must record it.)
(The atmosphere gets heated up.)
Great morning energy.
(Let us remind you. It's 7:30am local time.)
- Bravo!
- Fantastic!
(Thumbs up!)
(Passing by the beautiful scenery, they experience local culture.)
Why do we always sweat before we eat?
The atmosphere here is completely different again.
(The energy difference makes it difficult to believe...)
Super quiet.
(that this is just the next car.)
They are all traditional dishes from Huế.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
They were all pre-cooked, so they heated them in the microwave.
I guess you don't eat this.
You don't? Is it a bamboo stick?
You can't chew it.
(It's definitely not something you eat.)
Slide it out.
- It's similar to a fishcake.
- Right.
- It's good.
- But it's slightly different.
It's like the steamed bun we grew up eating.
Right.
What's inside?
I think it's beef.
It's a steamed bun you can't eat in Korea.
(Joon likes the authentic flavour.)
(Yum)
I love the dried shrimp in it.
There's shrimp.
(Bánh lọc is crispy dried shrimp wrapped in chewy dough.)
It's really good.
We played really hard, and it's still only 7:40am.
- We danced.
- It's going to be another long day.
Let's make it the longest day.
The day is really long.
I know.
What is it?
What is he doing?
- What is it?
- I know what it is.
What is it?
(Joon has no idea.)
Is he selling towels?
Why would he sell towels?
- Aren't those towels?
- You need the towel.
- After you do this.
- Why?
What can you do on a train?
Waterbomb?
Waterbomb on the train?
Why would you need a towel?
(Joon is very curious.)
- Do you want it?
- I will do that.
(Do you want to know?)
It's a foot bath.
No way. You can get a foot bath.
That's why you need the towel.
(Towel for your feet)
- This is fun.
- It's hilarious, isn't it?
(Warm water is delivered shortly after.)
Okay.
(The colour of the water is strangely dark.)
It smells like there are oriental herbs in it, doesn't it?
Yes.
We have to do everything we can do here.
Right.
It's hot! Gosh, it's hot!
- It's hot.
- You're young.
(Joon is still too young to endure the hot foot bath.)
My heels are in.
(He barely manages to get his heels in the water.)
I want to ask them to make the water even hotter.
Really? Your skin will cook.
Goodness.
(The beautiful scenery captures their attention.)
What a view!
(The panoramic blue sea)
- It's wild.
- Wild.
(Sunlight sparkles on the water like jewels.)
(The train runs through lush mountains, with the sea in view.)
(An emerald-blue beach comes into full view.)
It's like we're floating on the sea.
(It feels like floating on the sea.)
I feel like the train is going to fall off the cliff.
Terrifying.
- It's crazy.
- It's mad.
Look there. It's so beautiful.
What a spectacular view!
(Staring at the scenery that is like a watercolour painting,)
It's super romantic.
(they get drenched in the romantic mood.)
The ocean is huge.
Gosh, I can't believe...
The only flaw is that we can't sleep.
We can never sleep here.
(But Joon falls asleep right away.)
(His head keeps falling.)
(Hyun Moo can't take his eyes off the scenery.)
(What is everyone thinking while looking at the view?)
(Lang Co Station)
It's a small local station.
It's so pretty.
(A warm, familiar scene like Korea in the 90s)
Train to Chuncheon
(They get off the train to enjoy the short break.)
Let's get off the train.
(Lang Co Station)
The train is pretty.
It's a pretty train.
It's nicely decorated.
Do you want to take a photo?
Go stand there.
Right.
(Joon tries his best to look nice.)
(He's not frowning. He's focused.)
I took an amazing photo.
Did you?
(What do you think?)
(Groans)
(Did he take a photo of the train track?)
Let me try it.
(He can't say anything bad.)
(Hyun Moo's Concept: Cheerful)
Burst mode?
Let me see it.
I look like a madman.
"Whispering Corridors."
(2026 version "Whispering Hyun Moo")
You look like the gorilla stuck to a sign in LA.
Ice cream.
(Vietnam's heat makes them crave ice cream.)
Ice cream? It's ice cream.
There's watermelon and coconut.
- There's chocolate too.
- Chocolate.
(Cold ice cream will help them beat the heat.)
- I want the chocolate.
- I want the coconut.
It's good.
(The cold and sweet ice cream cools them down.)
(I need...)
(two of these.)
Here.
- One more.
We can communicate now.
Here.
It's 50 cents per ice cream.
- Thank you.
Should we eat it on the train?
- We should go inside.
- Let's eat it inside. It's hot.
(While Joon is in the restroom,)
(Hyun Moo eats his ice cream.)
(The chocolate coating falls.)
(I can't lose any of it.)
(He eats the fallen bits and finishes the ice cream too.)
Let's all go on a vacation
(Let's go to Huế!)
(Lang Co Station)
(As the train runs, the scenery changes.)
It's changed.
It's different.
(After 4 hours, they finally enter downtown Huế.)
(Let's see.)
What's the dish you must eat in Huế, Vietnam?
When you are in Huế, you must eat the following dishes.
Bún bò Huế is a rich and spicy beef rice noodle dish...
that is very popular in Huế.
That sounds delicious.
The noodles are round and fat,
and the rich and spicy lemongrass broth...
- This is great.
- satisfies the Korean palate.
- It sounds good, doesn't it?
- Bún bò Huế.
(It's a perfect dish for Koreans missing the taste of home.)
I think you mix rice in it.
(AI's 2nd recommendation is cơm hến.)
It's a freshwater clam mixed rice...
with crispy fried pork rind.
It's a Huế delicacy. You mix rice with peanuts and herbs.
(It's the local delicacy you can only eat in Huế.)
All right.
- Bún bò Huế, it is.
- Bún bò Huế.
- Spicy beef rice noodles.
Yes.
I am really craving something spicy.
(He searches for the restaurants that sell bún bò Huế.)
Closed?
What?
It's only 11am.
(It's 11am, and the shop is already closed.)
(They can't go to a bún bò Huế restaurant.)
Then where can we have good cơm hến?
The most popular local spot for cơm hến is Cơm Hến Hoa Đông.
- Cơm Hến Hoa Đông.
- It's 17 Hàn Mặc Tử Street.
It's 17 Hàn Mặc Tử Street. Cơm Hến Hoa Đông.
How does AI know everything?
I suddenly became really curious.
Does it know everything about the world?
It knows everything.
Finally, we're here. It's 11:30am.
(Departed Da Nang at 7:05am, Arrived in Huế at 11:30am)
- It took four hours. It's far.
- Yes.
It is.
- Bye. Thank you.
- Bye.
Now I feel like we're abroad.
- It does feel that way.
- Finally, I feel like we're abroad.
It's very authentic.
(The authentic scenery is complemented by the blue sky.)
It's beautiful.
(A classical French brick building)
(Huế Station)
It's nice.
(Welcome to Huế.)
- Goodness.
- Oh, my gosh.
So hot!
- Gosh.
- It's so hot.
This is Vietnam.
It's hot.
It's scorching hot.
I can't open my eyes.
So this is how hot it gets.
It's just 15 minutes away, so instead of getting a taxi,
why don't we ride a motorcycle?
- Since it's hot?
- Should we?
- Wouldn't that be better?
- That would be cool.
They are not aggressive, so they won't scam us.
Right?
If they grab you, it means they will scam you.
- They are not aggressive.
- They are not.
- "Hire us if you want." - They are passive.
Hello.
Here?
- Okay.
- Hoa Đông.
How much?
(It's not easy to communicate in English.)
How much is it?
(Even in Vietnamese, it's not easy to communicate.)
There's no point in asking them in Vietnamese.
- We...
- We can't understand the answer.
When we ask in Vietnamese, they answer in Vietnamese.
I'll use this.
How much?
(The translation app and calculator are travel essentials.)
It's about 25,000 dong.
It's cheap.
- Per person...
- Take a zero out.
It's 1.20 dollars.
- Okay.
- Nice. Wait.
- Hyun Moo.
- Yes?
Don't you want to wear sunscreen?
- Okay.
- You will get burned.
You will get seriously burned.
- Really? I never wear it.
- You have to.
(He's lazy, but he listens to his buddy.)
Hop on.
(They take a motorcycle instead of a taxi.)
Yes.
In Vietnam, people often ride motorcycles...
to move around narrow streets easily.
(A total of 77 million motorcycles are registered in Vietnam.)
This means 7 out of 10 people own a motorcycle.
(In Vietnam, motorcycles are a part of life.)
Let's go!
From Huế Station,
we're headed to the restaurant I searched on the train using AI.
This restaurant is known for...
a dish called cơm hến, which is like a freshwater clam soup.
So we will head to Cơm Hến Hoa Đông.
Joon's following us.
(Joon is following him.)
In front of me is...
the motorcycle taxi driver. You're supposed to hug him.
It's called Xe ôm here.
He's driving very safely.
(Xe ôm is a popular local transportation.)
It's scary on a motorcycle.
(Joon is scared to ride the motorcycle.)
Gosh, that's loud.
I wish he would go slower.
If I'm too scared, the driver...
might get annoyed, so I should stay quiet.
Nice.
(Half scared and half thrilled)
Aren't you scared?
I'm not scared. Are you scared?
I'm scared to ride in the back of a motorcycle.
Your muscles are only for showing off.
You're a chicken.
To be fair, it was really hot, but it's quite breezy now.
The sky is beautiful.
Huế is Gyeongju of Vietnam. It lives up to its fame, doesn't it?
There are lots of historic sites.
(Historic sites preserve traces of a bygone dynasty.)
(A cityscape in harmony with the sky)
This must be the downtown.
There's a college.
(Huế University)
(Staring)
- Wait, I know you!
- Have you ever seen it?
- Thank you!
- I love you!
She recognised me.
- You're an MC, right?
- Yes.
- You are Jun Hyun Moo, right?
Yes!
- Thank you.
She knows that I'm an MC.
(Turns out today is the university graduation day.)
Hello.
- Hello.
You remember the TV show?
- Yes!
- The name.
I saw you a lot.
Yes?
She's seen me many times.
I am Jun Hyun Moo,
the MC recognised by the Vietnamese.
(Overjoyed)
She's so shy that she can't talk.
(They enter the street with a more provincial atmosphere.)
It's beautiful.
It's a jungle here.
It's nice.
It's amazing here.
I feel like there would be a crocodile.
(After crossing a river where crocodiles might lurk,)
Hello.
(a quiet, peaceful neighbourhood comes into view.)
It's quiet.
Is it here?
(They arrive at the destination in the middle of a quiet town.)
Here. Yes.
What's this?
It appeared out of nowhere!
It's the only place filled with people.
It's incredible.
(It's the only busy place in the middle of a quiet town.)
(It's bustling with locals.)
Why is this the only busy restaurant?
(Unlike the other restaurants that are very empty,)
(this restaurant has a long waiting line.)
(And they are all locals too.)
There are lots of young people here.
(It's a popular local restaurant that sells cơm hến.)
It must be super popular.
They are all locals too.
(Their expectations grow as they see all the locals.)
- All right.
- Goodness.
Goodness.
Good grief.
This bag is so heavy.
You came here light, so why are you travelling heavy?
- It's driving me crazy.
- I don't get you.
- I don't get it either.
- I travel light.
This is crazy.
Learn from me.
- I will explain to you.
- Okay.
You saw it. All the other restaurants are empty,
- but this restaurant is packed.
- Right.
It means this restaurant has good food.
Do you see any Koreans? No, right?
- There's not one.
(They look around, but there are no Koreans.)
- What are you getting?
- What about you?
The freshwater clam rice.
Then I will have...
- noodles.
- Okay.
- Hello.
Hello.
(Nobody hears their cry.)
(Please take our order.)
(They raise their hands, but nobody pays attention.)
(Bothered)
Excuse me!
- Excuse me!
It's "cậu."
Excuse me!
- Cậu.
What does it mean?
It means "mister."
- Mister.
- Mister. "Cậu."
You speak a little bit of Korean.
Which one is the best menu?
The best is bún hến.
What? Bún hến?
Bún hến and...
Bún hến?
Try this one.
- This one?
- Yes.
- Try this one?
(Joon is fascinated to see a local speaking good Korean.)
- What? That's Korean.
- You speak good Korean.
- A little.
- "Try this one."
- This one?
(Cheered up by the local's recommendation,)
(he gives another try.)
One, one,
and one.
- Coke.
- Okay.
(Thanks to the kind locals, he orders food successfully.)
She speaks great Korean.
(Bún hến, freshwater clam noodles and cơm hến, freshwater clam rice)
This is cơm hến?
And what's this? Bún hến.
Okay.
It looks good though.
It looks good.
- This is freshwater clam.
- It's freshwater clam.
(Hến is similar to the Korean freshwater clam.)
(And hến broth is served with it.)
It looks good.
(Hyun Moo takes a sip of the broth first.)
It tastes just like the freshwater clam soup.
It tastes like the broth of Hamhung-style cold noodles.
It's nice.
- This is special.
- It's nice.
(Yum!)
It's good.
It's nice.
(Pleasantly surprised)
It's very similar to the Korean freshwater clam soup.
There's a generous amount of clams too.
The rice is so light and fluffy, it doesn't even fill you up.
I love it.
Cơm hến is a Vietnamese-style freshwater clam dish with rice.
Cơm means rice, and hến is freshwater clam.
(The Perfume River encircles Huế,)
(the lifeblood of the ancient capital.)
(Cơm hến is made with fresh hến caught in the Perfume River.)
(The fresh hến have rich umami and a delicate sweetness.)
(Locals sometimes sell the hến as soon as they catch them.)
(Hến is the ingredient beloved by the people of Hue.)
Add some spice.
I love the broth. Use this.
(They add the spice to maximize the flavour.)
(It's so good that it makes him nod.)
It's so good.
(Joon copies him and adds the spicy sauce too.)
They are all locals.
I think Koreans would love this.
Yes.
It tastes very familiar.
(The spice, which Koreans would love, enhances the flavour.)
(The travel buddies quietly focus on eating the food.)
(Immersed in the local scene, they enjoy the local flavour.)
What's this?
Okay.
(Bánh bèo)
(It's the Huế-style rice cake eaten with fish sauce.)
(He carefully scrapes the bottom of the small plate.)
There's rice cake.
Right.
(There's a soft and chewy rice cake.)
This is cool. What's this?
(That white thing is rice cake?)
(Isn't this cool, Moo Friends?)
(It looks delicious.)
(I want to go to Vietnam.)
(Please have a bite.)
I love it.
(The dried shrimp and fish sauce give it a harmonious flavour.)
The white part reminds me of the steamed rice roll skin.
It's the same. It's like the steamed rice roll skin.
(It's got the soft and chewy texture just like the Chinese rice roll.)
It looks like this.
It doesn't look special.
You add chillies to this.
(You add chillies to this.)
Chillies.
Then you pour the sauce.
(Then you pour the sauce.)
- To the rice cake.
- It's something new.
When you scoop it up, there's rice cake.
It looks like a side dish.
You can't eat this in Korea.
There's nothing similar to it.
This is really fun.
When you scoop it up, the rice cake gets lifted.
There's rice cake.
You eat like this.
(Spoon and camera)
(Hyun Moo, the professional YouTuber, doesn't miss anything.)
Isn't it good?
It's addictive.
They balanced the flavours so well.
This gives it a nice texture.
These pops in the mouth.
- It's packed with flavour, right?
- And the rice cake...
- wraps it all up.
- Right.
Right.
This is so new.
Business is booming.
This must be the only good restaurant.
Look at that queue.
(The waiting line is endless.)
(They must be filming something.)
(Where?)
Hello.
Lee Joon.
I've seen a movie he starred in.
It feels strange that they know me as an actor, not as an idol.
You successfully transitioned into an actor.
It feels strange.
(You are him, right?)
(Calm down, honey.)
I think...
It's good.
Vietnamese people have a real knack for good food.
The flavours are incredibly balanced.
We didn't know anything about Vietnamese food.
I know.
It's very different from the Vietnamese food...
we eat in Korea.
It's the most special dish I've eaten so far.
(Through this experience, they are learning about...)
(the flavour of Vietnam they didn't know about.)
It was true that you come to Vietnam for food.
(Immersed in the local scene,)
(they experienced Vietnamese food culture.)
It's amazing, isn't it?
I am surprised that I still haven't eaten pho here.
It feels like we are discovering new flavours.
- I know.
- That's what I love.
I want to experience failure just once,
- but we haven't failed once.
- No.
This is so satisfying.
(Cơm hến, bún hến, bánh bèo, and drink)
(Total: approximately 8 dollars)
It's 8 dollars for 2 people?
(Travel itinerary available on our official social media account)
(The last journey of the Vietnam trip)
My travel style might change.
It was a pollution-free trip.
(It's not over yet!)
It's not over yet!
(They will continue to search for a place without tourists.)
(They will go deeper into the local scene.)
- Really?
- Is it sold out?
(There's no backing out now.)
(If you can't find it, become a local!)
(They blend in perfectly with the locals!)
(Who's the local here?)
(They haggle quite well now.)
(They win her heart.)
(They've already become part of the local scene.)
Where are we going now?
(History is the highlight of any local travel experience!)
(Back to the Huế)
(They travel 100 years back in time.)
- Shut your mouth!
- Shut it! Slap him!
(A spectacular trip back in time with the bumbling kings)
(In Huế, past and present coexist.)
(Into the heart of Vietnam!)
(And...)
(what happened to Hyun Moo?)
(Every Sunday at 10:30pm)